<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Thursday on Tryna Get Less Fat, Yo.</title>
    <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/tags/thursday/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Thursday on Tryna Get Less Fat, Yo.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>©2021 cliff1976.  &lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fat.cliff1976.net/tags/thursday/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 05 14</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-05-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-05-14/</guid>
      <description>Another kooky GPX track. Harumph. No way I did 9+ km yesterday morning before work.
Some thoughts on schaffen: see my post on bergberg.net.
And it looks like the city has some schaffen planned for our street.
Snaps:
Route:
Machine(s): none (street) Time: 0:56 Distance: probably around 5 km Calories: 427 Calories from fat: 36% Average Heart Rate: 109 Maximum Heart Rate: 127 Fat Burn: 0:47 Fitness: 0:08 Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 05 07</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-05-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-05-07/</guid>
      <description>Oops, forgot to bring my watch on my walk, so I have no heart rate stats for this one. Also, nothing leapt out at me as photo-worthy. But at least I discovered the Gemüsebagels at Der Beck are pretty good.
Route:
Time: 1:10 Distance: 6 km Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 04 09</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-04-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-04-09/</guid>
      <description>Another beautiful day.
Snaps:
Route:
Machine(s): none (street) Time: 73 mins Distance: 6 km Calories: 610 Calories from fat: 29% Average Heart Rate: 113 Maximum Heart Rate: 134 Fat Burn: 33 mins Fitness: 40 min Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 04 02</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-04-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-04-02/</guid>
      <description>Another beautiful day. Got started earlier than normal thanks to an 8:00 meeting. 3rd in a row. Criminy.
Figured out that a brisk walk to/from work, if I ever go back there, is nearly exactly a 30-minute affair (using the bike paths and avoiding traffic lights).
Route:
Machine(s): none (street) Time: 66 mins Distance: 6.6 km Calories: 641 Calories from fat: 32% Average Heart Rate: 113 Maximum Heart Rate: 142 Fat Burn: 52 mins Fitness: 24 mins Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 03 26</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-03-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-03-26/</guid>
      <description>Another beautiful day. Finally made it up to the top of the Dreifaltigkeitsberg. Walked down the east face of the hill towards the Regen banks and made my way from there back home via the Nibelungenbrücke.
Some snaps:
Route:
Machine(s): none (street) Time: 1 hour 37 mins Distance: 8.02 km Calories: 946 Calories from fat: 24% Average Heart Rate: 121 Maximum Heart Rate: 150 Fat Burn: 26 mins Fitness: 71 mins Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 03 19</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-03-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-03-19/</guid>
      <description>Same weather as yesterday, but without the clouds. Nice mix of city and waterways.
Route:
Machine(s): none (street) Time: 58 mins Distance: 5.05 km Calories: 466 Calories from fat: 34% Average Heart Rate: 111 Maximum Heart Rate: 127 Fat Burn: 45 mins Fitness: 13 mins Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 03 12</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-03-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-03-12/</guid>
      <description>Machine(s): elliptical Time: 40 minutes Distance: 4.32 km Calories: 369 Calories from fat: 32% Average Heart Rate: 118 Maximum Heart Rate: 123 Fat Burn: 33 minutes Fitness: 7 minutes Weight: not measured </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 03 05</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-03-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-03-05/</guid>
      <description>Machine(s): elliptical Time: 40 minutes Distance: 4.24 km Calories: 345 Calories from fat: 32% Average Heart Rate: 114 Maximum Heart Rate: 121 Fat Burn: 33 minutes Fitness: 7 minutes Weight: not measured </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 02 26</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-02-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-02-26/</guid>
      <description>Forgot to weigh myself; was a running a bit short on time and I didn&amp;rsquo;t go at all on Wednesday.
Machine(s): elliptical Settings: incline 1, resistance 3 Time: 37 minutes Distance: 4.5 km Calories: 323 Calories from fat: 30% Average Heart Rate: 115 Maximum Heart Rate: 127 Fat Burn: 20 minutes Fitness: 16 minutes Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 02 20</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-02-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-02-20/</guid>
      <description>Got there right on time this time. Pick of the machines.
Machine(s): elliptical Settings: incline 1, resistance 5 and 3 Time: 40 minutes Distance: 4.5 km Calories: 375 Calories from fat: 31% Average Heart Rate: 115 Maximum Heart Rate: 128 Fat Burn: 26 minutes Fitness: 14 minutes Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 02 13</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-02-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-02-13/</guid>
      <description>I knew Friday wasn&amp;rsquo;t going to be an option due to a work meeting at 07:30. This messes up my whole MWF vibe, but it won&amp;rsquo;t be the last time.
Machine(s): elliptical Settings: incline 1, resistance Time: 41 minutes Distnce: 5.15 km Calories: 444 Calories from fat: 18% Average Heart Rate: 130 Maximum Heart Rate: 143 Fat Burn: 1 minutes Fitness: 41 minutes Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
