<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Walks on cliff1976</title>
    <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Walks on cliff1976</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://fat.cliff1976.net/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>10 somewhat creepy km in Regensburg</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/20220724/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/20220724/</guid>
      <description>After returning from Iași on July 8th, my fitness regimen was hindered by a few different things:
weather (it&amp;rsquo;s been pretty hot!), and intense work stuff (which is why I scheduled the business trip the way I did), but mostly mein innerer Schweinehund I wanted to set off this morning on a bike ride, but I found a flat tire waiting for me. So I took a stroll instead.
Snaps First I walked over to VyVu to try to see what their outdoor seating options are&amp;hellip;missing some Banh Mi in my life ever since their place in the Markthalle on Dachauplatz closed earlier this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About 6 km in grueling heat</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/20220702/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/20220702/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m in Iași for a couple weeks and just hit the half-way point.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been visiting this city on business a few times per year since 2006, but usually just for part of a week. As near as I can tell, this is only the third or fourth time I&amp;rsquo;ve been over a weekend, and only the third time not during the winter. And I&amp;rsquo;m staying in a new (to me) hotel quite close to the office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First (recorded) walk of the year</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/20220206/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/20220206/</guid>
      <description>Due to travel and holidays I kinda took 3 months off of my irregularly scheduled programming. Even though there was some unscheduled exercise walking around in new and familiar places, there probably wasn&amp;rsquo;t enough in general, and that&amp;rsquo;s not good.
So, here&amp;rsquo;s the first attempt at getting back up on that horse, off of which I kinda threw myself.
Snaps Route Distance: 7.25 km Time: 1:30 Calories: 852 Calories from fat: 25 % Average Heart Rate: 119 Maximum Heart Rate: 139 Fat Burn: 0:27 Fitness: 1:02 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Haha, phone.  Very funny.</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/20210401/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/20210401/</guid>
      <description>I think my phone&amp;rsquo;s GPS was playing a prank on me. This shouldn&amp;rsquo;t have been a 7 km walk.
Route Distance: 7.1 km Time: 1:12 Calories: 560 Calories from fat: 37 % Average Heart Rate: 108 Maximum Heart Rate: 123 Fat Burn: 1:06 Fitness: 0:06 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/20210330/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/20210330/</guid>
      <description>Last minute decision, kinda, to run over to a buddy&amp;rsquo;s place to pick up some fruit preserves he made and kept for us. Cut it kinda close with regard to the curfew in place due to Regensburg&amp;rsquo;s infection rates.
Route Distance: ~5 km </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/20210327/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/20210327/</guid>
      <description>Just a Saturday shopping trip on foot. I think the longer the longer you stand around in one place (like while waiting for mantı at Lezizel), the less reliable the GPS readings become.
Route Distance: 4.95 km Time: 1:38 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IT BEGINS</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/20210326/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/20210326/</guid>
      <description>Die Spargelzeit, that is.
German asparagus is available at REWE near us. Lass den Spargelwahn krachen.
Snaps That building across the street from REWE and Candis Park is getting bigger everytime I walk by.
Not all of the stuff shown here is domestic or even regional. But at least the white asparagus in the yellow plastic bag is the REWE Regional brand. So it won&amp;rsquo;t be much longer until everyone&amp;rsquo;s griping about the workers imported from Eastern European countries bringing Covid in with them to steal German bikes and not appreciably drop the prices on a Pfund of asparagus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/20210324/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/20210324/</guid>
      <description>A quiet, gray riverside morning. With the bonus of an unexpected Irish Wolfhound.
Snaps Route Distance: 6.2 km Time: 1:17 Calories: 668 Calories from fat: 32 % Average Heart Rate: 114 Maximum Heart Rate: 129 Fat Burn: 0:49 Fitness: 0:28 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021-03-18</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/20210318/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/20210318/</guid>
      <description>Got up way too early today. Why not turn it into a walk? The timezone shift is coming soon; might as well embrace the sunlight.
Snaps The OTH pond was nice and still.
I liked the irony of both a car and a bike swerving onto the sidewalk to drive around the crew applying a Fahrradstrasse sign on the street.
Route Distance: 6.5 km Time: 1:30 Calories: 781 Calories from fat: 30% Average Heart Rate: 114 Maximum Heart Rate: 134 Fat Burn: 1:16 Fitness: 0:14 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blood Drive...walk, actually.</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/20210316/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/20210316/</guid>
      <description>It was time to donate blood again today.
I didn&amp;rsquo;t get my morning walk in, so I took a three kilometer stroll up to the Jahnstadion after work and got there dreadfully early for my 18:30 appointment. So I kept strolling and killed a little time, padding out my walk to five kilometers.
I had my phone set to mark my position every 30 seconds, and that makes my traversal of the parking lot rows look sloppy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pastry Loop</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/20210314/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/20210314/</guid>
      <description>We took a walk today instead of my usual Sunday bike ride. We stopped in at Opera in der Prüfeninger Straße and scooped up some (counter-productive) baked goods. It reminded us that we are really looking forward to a time when we can have some Kaffee und Kuchen out at a place like Opera.
Snaps Route Distance: 8.42 km Time: 1:47 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021-03-12</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/2021-03-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/2021-03-12/</guid>
      <description>Windy and rainy. But I discovered a bike path to Oberhinkofen near the SE corner of this route, and a BMX &amp;ldquo;Dirtpark&amp;rdquo;, should I ever feel so inclined.
Also gas prices &amp;ndash; WAY UP.
Snaps Route Distance: 5.0 km Time: 1:06 Calories: 571 Calories from fat: 30 % Average Heart Rate: 114 Maximum Heart Rate: 127 Fat Burn: 0:30 Fitness: 0:36 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/2021-03-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/2021-03-09/</guid>
      <description>That construction project across from the big REWE is going up like gangbusters.
Also 4 people in Hot Chicken at once. Are they saving up for some actual chicken?
Whoa, look at the time on this one!
Snaps Route Distance: 4.9 km Time: 1:11:11 Calories: 484 Calories from fat: 38% Average Heart Rate: 103 Maximum Heart Rate: 118 Fat Burn: 1:08 Fitness: 1:02 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grocery Run through Das Dörnberg</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/2021-03-02-das-doernberg/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/2021-03-02-das-doernberg/</guid>
      <description>I hate that it&amp;rsquo;s das Dörnberg. Man, this place is really growing. It&amp;rsquo;s a couple years too late, but BLTN, I guess.
Snaps I bet they&amp;rsquo;re going to need the services of the A-Team.
Route Distance: 6.72 km Time: 1:45 Calories: 678 Calories from fat: 38% Average Heart Rate: 101 Maximum Heart Rate: 123 Fat Burn: 1:25 Fitness: 0:20 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Regenstauf to Ramspau and back</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/2021-02-27-regenstauf-ramspau/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/2021-02-27-regenstauf-ramspau/</guid>
      <description>We drove about 15 minutes north to the town of Regenstauf to shop at Quantum Satis — same as last weekend. This time, we did a longer walk afterwards and brought a pal (newish to Regensburg) along for the shop and chat. It was a nice day for it. The original route would have led us into a hilly, muddy (owing to the rain the previous night), woody area, so we stuck to the road and even went a little farther than expected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021-02-24</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/2021-02-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/2021-02-24/</guid>
      <description>You think it&amp;rsquo;s walking past the water and electric utility office building that&amp;rsquo;s causing my GPS readings to go nuts, or is it maybe weather-related? It was a very foggy morning. Could that be it?
Route Distance: 6.0? km Time: 1.03 Calories: 630 Calories from fat: 26% Average Heart Rate: 122 Maximum Heart Rate: 140 Fat Burn: 0:19 Fitness: 0:43 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021-02-23</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/2021-02-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/2021-02-23/</guid>
      <description>I like that I can be awake and out for a walk around the time the sun starts his day, too.
Snaps Sun up over Kumpfmühl.
I would not have picked Bitter&amp;rsquo; O as the name of my confectionery.
Route Distance: 6.0 km Time: 1:22 Calories: 580 Calories from fat: 39 % Average Heart Rate: 104 Maximum Heart Rate: 125 Fat Burn: 1:15 Fitness: 0:07 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marshy Storchy Regen Riverbanks</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/20210220-regenstauf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/20210220-regenstauf/</guid>
      <description>We took the car up to Regenstauf on a very small shopping trip. We headed specifically to Quantum Satis, packaging-free store. They have a LOT of the stuff we use on a daily basis available in bulk. So even though it costs a lot more (compared to the typical grocery store fare), I&amp;rsquo;d like to start refilling pantry staples from that store, without incurring packaging waste.
Side note: there is another great packaging-free store in downtown Regensburg &amp;ndash; Füllgut (which has a nice pun in its name).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loop around the canals</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/2021-01-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/2021-01-31/</guid>
      <description>Bright sunny day and cold, but not bitterly so. The sun and the activity warmed us up such that a brief stop in the shade (or the wind over the dam) was plenty to cool us down again.
Lots of other people had the same idea &amp;ndash; taking advantage of the weather today. Let&amp;rsquo;s hope that doesn&amp;rsquo;t result in another Corona spike &amp;ndash; the extended lockdown has been working pretty well this time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January 19, 2021</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/2021-01-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/2021-01-19/</guid>
      <description>Route Distance: 4.65 km Time: 0:58 Calories: 517 Calories from fat: 28% Average Heart Rate: 115 Maximum Heart Rate: 127 Fat Burn: 0:51 Fitness: 0:07 Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/2021-01-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/2021-01-17/</guid>
      <description>Ya gotta love that the Edeka in the Hauptbahnhof is open on Sundays and everyday from 6am to midnight!
Route Distance: 9.54 km Time: 2:13 Calories: 1190 Calories from fat: 35% Average Heart Rate: 115 Maximum Heart Rate: 136 Fat Burn: 1:54 Fitness: 0:19 Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/2021-01-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/2021-01-16/</guid>
      <description>Route Don&amp;rsquo;t trust the GPS on this one; the track is pretty messed up.
Distance: 8.17 km </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/2021-01-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/2021-01-14/</guid>
      <description>Route Distance: 8.17 km Time: 1:09 Calories: 504 Calories from fat: 37% Average Heart Rate: 105 Maximum Heart Rate: 119 Fat Burn: 1:06 Fitness: 0:03 Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/2021-01-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/2021-01-12/</guid>
      <description>Route Distance: 3 km Time: 0:30 Calories: 290 Calories from fat: 28% Average Heart Rate: 121 Maximum Heart Rate: 134 Fat Burn: 0:12 Fitness: 0:18 Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/20210112/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/20210112/</guid>
      <description>It was a day off, so why not take a stroll in the snowy rain?
Snaps Route Distance: 8.25 km Time: 1:52 Calories: 1045 Calories from fat: 27% Average Heart Rate: 118 Maximum Heart Rate: 140 Fat Burn: 0:49 Fitness: 1:03 Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fußenbergtrail to Hauzenstein and back</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/2021-01-02-fussenberg-hauzenstein/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/2021-01-02-fussenberg-hauzenstein/</guid>
      <description>First walk of the year!
Some local pals suggested this route through the woods starting outside of Wenzenbach, heading north. It was very pretty, and would have been quite short, but for the icy trails. Much of it runs parallel to a few creeks, so there was a lot of moisture to contend with &amp;ndash; and much of it had turned to ice.
Notes need new hiking boots (soles are pretty much gone on mine) consider buying &amp;ldquo;hiking poles&amp;rdquo; (&amp;quot;Wanderstöcke&amp;quot;) bringing crampons along next time getting a thermos; really could have used a warm beverage, like hot chocolate tea/coffee Glühwein (make Sarah drive) Snaps Route Distance: about 7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/2020-12-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/2020-12-30/</guid>
      <description>Last walk of the year!
Snaps Route Distance: 8.5 km Time: 1:48 Calories: 1027 Calories from fat: 30% Average Heart Rate: 119 Maximum Heart Rate: 131 Fat Burn: 0:54 Fitness: 0:54 Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/2020-12-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/2020-12-27/</guid>
      <description>Frost! First overnight one of the season, I think. I spotted frozen puddles in places on my walk this morning.
Snaps Donkey Republic bikes not far from home!
Frosty trainyard
This was a parking garage less than a year ago.
The mosque is coming along nicely.
Here&amp;rsquo;s another big pit of a construction site.
Philosophical graffiti:
Is it a peaceful place to work or not?
Route Distance: 9.75 km Time: 2:30 Calories: 1173 Calories from fat: 33% Average Heart Rate: 107 Maximum Heart Rate: 134 Fat Burn: 1:27 Fitness: 1:07 Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/2020-12-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/2020-12-20/</guid>
      <description>It was hovering around freezing, and kinda wet, and that made me nervous about a long bike ride and the potential for a wipe-out, so I opted for a walk instead.
Snaps I don&amp;rsquo;t know how long it&amp;rsquo;s been there, but there&amp;rsquo;s a Bucherzelle at the Andreasstadel in Stadtamhof now. Looks like they&amp;rsquo;ve had trouble with people using it improperly. I hope that behavior doesn&amp;rsquo;t doom it.
I walked up to the top of the Dreifaltigkeitsberg.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/2020-12-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/2020-12-15/</guid>
      <description>Just a post-work pre-lockdown grocery run to the big Rewe. No pics; it was full-on dark.
Route Distance: 5.4 km Time: 1:11 Calories: 558 Calories from fat: 33% Average Heart Rate: 108 Maximum Heart Rate: 120 Fat Burn: 0:52 Fitness: 0:19 Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/2020-12-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/2020-12-13/</guid>
      <description>I was going to do another shorty 20 or maybe 30km bike ride today, but the weather prediction changed and I decided that if there was a chance of rain and temperatures hovering around freezing, I&amp;rsquo;d rather be on foot. So I did a long walk instead.
Snaps Got a new sweatshirt for my recent birthday from my parents. That thing is warm. Was great today for this long, dreary walk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/2020-12-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/2020-12-11/</guid>
      <description>I needed to walk into town to buy some beer and lunchmeat. So I took the long way.
The canal under the Grieser Steg was a pretty shade of green.
When I crossed into Stadtamhof, I saw the Spital brewery is advertising a Halbe Radler with a motorcycling monkey logo. I hope there&amp;rsquo;s an inside joke in there I&amp;rsquo;m just not getting.
Route Distance: 6.4 km Time: 1:07 Calories: 770 Calories from fat: 30% Average Heart Rate: 113 Maximum Heart Rate: 128 Fat Burn: 0:20 Fitness: 0:47 Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accidental 12k day</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/12-km-20201209/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/12-km-20201209/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve been walking a neighbor dog a couple days a week. I did a nice long one with her on a day when we also did the grocery shopping on foot. So there were almost thirteen that day. I only wore the heart rate monitor for the dog walk part of the day (in red solid lines).
Route Distance: 5 km Time: 1:17 Calories: 612 Calories from fat: 33% Average Heart Rate: 109 Maximum Heart Rate: 130 Fat Burn: 0:52 Fitness: 0:25 Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>November Impressions</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/november-impressions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/november-impressions/</guid>
      <description>It was a beautiful Sunday morning &amp;ndash; first one around here in recent memory.
Nice pictures are avilable on the Regensblog.
Route Distance: 6 km Time: 1:41 Calories: 789 Calories from fat: 39% Average Heart Rate: 108 Maximum Heart Rate: 140 Fat Burn: 1:36 Fitness: 0:05 Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bonndorf Exploration Part 2</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/bonndorf-exploration-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/bonndorf-exploration-part-2/</guid>
      <description>Took advantage of some nice weather here (well, mostly &amp;ndash; we got a little rained on towards the end).
Nice pictures are avilable on the Regensblog.
Routes:
Distance: 6.39 km Time: 2:37 Calories: 871 Calories from fat: 46% Average Heart Rate: 96 Maximum Heart Rate: 125 Fat Burn: 2:33 Fitness: 0:04 Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bonndorf Exploration Part 1</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/bonndorf-exploration-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/bonndorf-exploration-part-1/</guid>
      <description>We arrived in Bonndorf for an 8-day stay at a Ferienwohnung. On our second day, we set out exploring in and around the town and the valley below it.
Nice pictures are avilable on the Regensblog.
Routes:
Distance: 6.29 km Time: 1:37 Calories: 564 Calories from fat: 42% Average Heart Rate: 98 Maximum Heart Rate: 130 Fat Burn: 1:28 Fitness: 0:09 Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lorchhausen to Lorch in two parts</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/lorchhausen-to-lorch-in-two-parts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/lorchhausen-to-lorch-in-two-parts/</guid>
      <description>Part One was just me exploring Monday morning in the hills above our Ferienwohnung in Lorchhausen.
Part Two was the two of us going higher up and further east (all the way into Lorch for lunch) and back along the river on Wednesday.
Routes:
Part One:
Distance: 5.79 km Time: 2:00 Calories: 1024 Calories from fat: 30% Average Heart Rate: 114 Maximum Heart Rate: 147 Fat Burn: 1:13 Fitness: 0:47 Weight: not weighed Part Two:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KEINE Kulinarische Weinwanderung</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/20200925-keine-kulinarische-weinwanderung/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/20200925-keine-kulinarische-weinwanderung/</guid>
      <description>Sure felt weird doing this Freinsheim walk by myself, and not with any of the usual suspects, or 10,000 other wine and food enthusiasts.
More pictures on the Regensblog, sooner or later.
Route:
Distance: 6.29 km Time: 1:21 Calories: 643 Calories from fat: 37% Average Heart Rate: 104 Maximum Heart Rate: 121 Fat Burn: 1:19 Fitness: 0:14 Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ciao Bella Asparagi!</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/20200411_sat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/20200411_sat/</guid>
      <description>Scored fresh, local, green asparagus at the Donaumarkt &amp;ndash; grilled it for dinner for the second day in a row. Was a great accompaniment to the Bärlauchrisotto Sarah made.
Desweiteren we went to Tutto Italiano for the first time and found some stuff that Il Mercato does not carry. Including wine from Badia a Coltibuono! What a score!
Two routes, 11.3 km total today:
The splotchy bits are our wanderings inside the Lukullus Polish market on Greflingerstraße and Tutto Italiano and REWE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>That escalated quickly.</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/the_week_ending_20200410/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/the_week_ending_20200410/</guid>
      <description>I didn&amp;rsquo;t expect this week&amp;rsquo;s walk to be so&amp;hellip;threatening.
This week&amp;rsquo;s routes (minus Thursday, which mysteriously went missing):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Großprüfening and back</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/20200405-to-gross-pruefening-and-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/20200405-to-gross-pruefening-and-back/</guid>
      <description>I knew I wanted to talk a long Sunday stroll, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t expect it would turn into a 10-mile (16-kilometer) multi-hour deal. Got a little sore by the end of it. More pictures on the Regensblog post about it.
Route:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Week&#39;s Walks</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/walks_20200330-0403/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/walks_20200330-0403/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s where I&amp;rsquo;ve been.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bad Abbach 2020 03 20</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/bad_abbach_2020-03-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/walks/bad_abbach_2020-03-20/</guid>
      <description>This was the last chance to leave town before the Ausgangsbeschränkung went into effect at midnight tonight, so we took it. We also saw
where our pal gets all those beautiful mystical forest shots of his dogs, and some ancient Celtic mystery forest stuff [cue the spooky music], and the foundations of an old Roman bathhouse as the ruins from a Villa Rustica Route:
Time: 121 mins Distance: 7.7 km </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
