<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tuesday on Tryna Get Less Fat, Yo.</title>
    <link>/tags/tuesday/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tuesday on Tryna Get Less Fat, Yo.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>©2020 cliff1976.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="/tags/tuesday/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 05 19</title>
      <link>/posts/workouts/2020-05-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/workouts/2020-05-19/</guid>
      <description>I walked into work, grabbed some masks from my desk the company had set out for me, and came back via the supermarket. It was longer and slower, but I bought groceries, ran an errand, and even saw another person in the office, in person &amp;ndash; did not expect that. I might have surprised her, too.
Lone Snap:

That mosque near work is coming along nicely. Looking forward to their lunch counter opening&amp;hellip;if I ever return to working in the office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 05 12</title>
      <link>/posts/workouts/2020-05-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/workouts/2020-05-12/</guid>
      <description>GPS went nutty again today. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if
 it&amp;rsquo;s something atmospheric, or the satellites were out of alignment, or the case on my phone, or whether or not the phone&amp;rsquo;s in a pocket or loose in my hand, or an intermittent hardware problem is wreaking havoc  But I for sure did not follow the exact path shown in the route.
I did find the use of rubber gloves hanging from the bridge the near florist&amp;rsquo;s shop under the bridge quite attractive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 04 14</title>
      <link>/posts/workouts/2020-04-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/workouts/2020-04-14/</guid>
      <description>A somewhat less beautiful day. I went for a walk after work, instead of before it. It was overcast and cool, but still okay for getting a strenuous walk in.
Snaps:
 
Route:

Machine(s): none (street) Time: 66 mins Distance: 5.38 km Calories: 493 Calories from fat: 36% Average Heart Rate: 107 Maximum Heart Rate: 118 Fat Burn: 63 mins Fitness: 3 min Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 04 07</title>
      <link>/posts/workouts/2020-04-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/workouts/2020-04-07/</guid>
      <description>Another beautiful day.
Had to wait for a train in the Hafengebiet. Crossed a waterway along a train bridge — next time I think I&amp;rsquo;ll go all the way to Schwabelweis for a longer walk. Weird junky art stuff near the industrial recycling place right at the path leading from the bridge back down onto the south bank of the Danube.
Snaps:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 03 31</title>
      <link>/posts/workouts/2020-03-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/workouts/2020-03-31/</guid>
      <description>Another beautiful day. Got started earlier than normal thanks to an 8:00 meeting.
Route:

Machine(s): none (street) Time: 59 mins Distance: 5.17 km Calories: 476 Calories from fat: 33% Average Heart Rate: 111 Maximum Heart Rate: 123 Fat Burn: 40 mins Fitness: 19 mins Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 03 24</title>
      <link>/posts/workouts/2020-03-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/workouts/2020-03-24/</guid>
      <description>Another beautiful day. Went north and east near Sedanstraße and back through the Candis Park. Kind of an interesting mix of pretty, ugly, and ultra-modern dwellings all in this area.



Route:

Machine(s): none (street) Time: 56 mins Distance: not sure (OsmAnd forced a reboot) Calories: 476 Calories from fat: 33% Average Heart Rate: 114 Maximum Heart Rate: 126 Fat Burn: 41 mins Fitness: 14 mins Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 03 17</title>
      <link>/posts/workouts/2020-03-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/workouts/2020-03-17/</guid>
      <description>Happy Shamrock Shake Day! :(
We walked up and down the south bank of the Danube awhile.
Machine(s): none (street) Time: 52 mins Distance: unknown Calories: 300 Calories from fat: 41% Average Heart Rate: 104 Maximum Heart Rate: 123 Fat Burn: 42 mins Fitness: 0 mins Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 02 18</title>
      <link>/posts/workouts/2020-02-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/workouts/2020-02-18/</guid>
      <description>A little late getting started today, but my first meeting (working from home) was not until 09:30, so NBD. After this workout, I adjusted my watches settings to reflect my weight of 114 kg (it was set at 123 kg from my last doctor visit).
Machine(s): elliptical Settings: incline 1, resistance 3 Time: 62 minutes Distance: 6.60 km Calories: 640 Calories from fat: 29% Average Heart Rate: 127 Maximum Heart Rate: 140 Fat Burn: 34 minutes Fitness: 28 minutes Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>