<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Monday on Tryna Get Less Fat, Yo.</title>
    <link>/tags/monday/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Monday on Tryna Get Less Fat, Yo.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>©2021 cliff1976.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="/tags/monday/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 06 01</title>
      <link>/posts/workouts/2020-06-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/workouts/2020-06-01/</guid>
      <description>Holiday weekend! (Fronleichnam, I think). I took my first walk through the Evangelischer Zentralfriedhof, which had a nice mix of sun and shade. I was kind of expecting more activity in there due to the holiday, but there was no one stirring.
Snaps:

The pit between Alberstraße and Ernst-Reuter-Platz is now fully empty; still don&amp;rsquo;t know what&amp;rsquo;s going in there.

Absolutely nothing happening at Hauptbahnhof, which felt weird, even for a public holiday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 05 25</title>
      <link>/posts/workouts/2020-05-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/workouts/2020-05-25/</guid>
      <description>Snaps:

Think of all the great grilled dinners we could have with these!

&amp;ldquo;Please wait to be seated&amp;rdquo; arrives in Germany with Corona.

Coming Home has taken over the space from &amp;ldquo;zum Sterischen Eck.&amp;rdquo; Hope it doesn&amp;rsquo;t suck.

Sweet upholstery on this Ente!
Route:

Machine(s): none (street) Time: 1:07 Distance: 5.27 km Calories: 502 Calories from fat: 36% Average Heart Rate: 107 Maximum Heart Rate: 122 Fat Burn: 1:03 Fitness: 0:04 Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 05 11</title>
      <link>/posts/workouts/2020-05-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/workouts/2020-05-11/</guid>
      <description>Threatening to rain all day today, and it actually did — a few drops at least on the way to REWE to get some groceries before work.
Flowers look nice at Luitpoldstraße and Sternbergstraße.
Also La Bona I mean &amp;ldquo;Orient Imbiss&amp;rdquo; has pita bread for sale on shelves on the street.
Snaps:



Route:

Machine(s): none (street) Time: 1:11 Distance: 5.4 km Calories: 494 Calories from fat: 37% Average Heart Rate: 104 Maximum Heart Rate: 118 Fat Burn: 1:07 mins Fitness: 4 mins Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 04 27</title>
      <link>/posts/workouts/2020-04-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/workouts/2020-04-27/</guid>
      <description>A cloudy, overcast morning. I was hoping for some nice sunrise edge-of-cloud views, but I think I was too late off the mark to get them. Instead I discovered a new (to me) tiny park almost directly south of our house. Also, I forgot to start my route tracker, so I missed the first 500 meters or so of the route. Dang it.
Snaps:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 04 21</title>
      <link>/posts/workouts/2020-04-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/workouts/2020-04-20/</guid>
      <description>Took an evening walk with Sarah instead of my usual morning solo walk. Saw a few nice sunset scenes and discovered a hops garden in the Innere Osten neighborhood.
Snaps: 
 
Route:

Machine(s): none (street) Time: 1:25 Distance: 5.35 km Calories: 632 Calories from fat: 35% Average Heart Rate: 107 Maximum Heart Rate: 119 Fat Burn: 1:17 Fitness: 8 min Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 04 13</title>
      <link>/posts/workouts/2020-04-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/workouts/2020-04-13/</guid>
      <description>Another beautiful day. A Schnitzeljagd of sorts, even.
Weltenburger am Dom is closed, apparently not even doing take-out, but the Kreuzschänke is accepting carry-out orders. I like that they encourage their patrons to bring their own food storage containers to reduce waste.
Also, the Spanier im Bruckmandl is no more. Some kind of Currywurst joint is there now?
Snaps:







 
Route:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 04 06</title>
      <link>/posts/workouts/2020-04-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/workouts/2020-04-06/</guid>
      <description>Another beautiful day.
Got started later than normal. Yesterday was a 16km stroll, so today&amp;rsquo;s walk of only 5.2km and starting later felt justified.
Snaps:






Route:

Machine(s): none (street) Time: 58 mins Distance: 5.2 km Calories: 449 Calories from fat: 36% Average Heart Rate: 108 Maximum Heart Rate: 119 Fat Burn: 57 mins Fitness: 1 min Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 03 30</title>
      <link>/posts/workouts/2020-03-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/workouts/2020-03-30/</guid>
      <description>Another beautiful day.
Route:

Machine(s): none (street) Time: 63 mins Distance: 7 km Calories: 496 Calories from fat: 34% Average Heart Rate: 109 Maximum Heart Rate: 130 Fat Burn: 55 mins Fitness: 8 mins Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 03 23</title>
      <link>/posts/workouts/2020-03-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/workouts/2020-03-22/</guid>
      <description>Another beautiful day. Went south and east along Alfons-Auer-Straße. Nothing spectacular to see there, really, but the Edeka on Hornstraße is pretty easy to reach from there.
Route:

Machine(s): none (street) Time: 45 mins Distance: 5.44 km Calories: 434 Calories from fat: 28% Average Heart Rate: 121 Maximum Heart Rate: 131 Fat Burn: 9 mins Fitness: 46 mins Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 03 02</title>
      <link>/posts/workouts/2020-03-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/workouts/2020-03-02/</guid>
      <description>Weighed in, since I&amp;rsquo;d skipped it last week.
Machine(s): elliptical Settings: incline 1, resistance 3 Time: 38 minutes Distance: 4.5 km Calories: 318 Calories from fat: 32% Average Heart Rate: 112 Maximum Heart Rate: 127 Fat Burn: 29 minutes Fitness: 9 minutes Weight: 113 kg (no change) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 02 24</title>
      <link>/posts/workouts/2020-02-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/workouts/2020-02-24/</guid>
      <description>Felt like it was harder to stay in the target heart range &amp;ndash; maybe because of the four-day gap since the previous workout. I may need to start going more than 3 days a week, which also means maybe going on at least one weekend day, eating into shopping time on Saturdays, or being crowded on Sundays. Yuck.
Machine(s): elliptical Settings: incline 1, resistance 3 Time: 37 minutes Distance: 4.5 km Calories: 362 Calories from fat: 28% Average Heart Rate: 121 Maximum Heart Rate: 133 Fat Burn: 12 minutes Fitness: 25 minutes Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 02 10</title>
      <link>/posts/workouts/2020-02-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/workouts/2020-02-10/</guid>
      <description>Gotta make sure my chest is good and wet before I get started. The watch was having trouble reading my pulse (although the Precor elliptical thing appeared to have no problem&amp;hellip;).
Machine(s): elliptical Settings: incline: 1 resistance: 8 Time: 41 minutes Calories: 324 Calories from fat: 29% Average Heart Rate: 116 Maximum Heart Rate: 124 Fat Burn: 14 minutes Fitness: 23 minutes Weight: not measured </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 02 03</title>
      <link>/posts/workouts/2020-02-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/workouts/2020-02-03/</guid>
      <description>Ugh. The first one. And it&amp;rsquo;s a Monday.
Machine(s): elliptical Settings: dunno Time: 42 minutes Calories: 381 Calories from fat: 30% Average Heart Rate: 117 Maximum Heart Rate: 131 Fat burn: 23 minutes Fitness: 19 minutes Weight: not measured </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>