<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wednesday on Tryna Get Less Fat, Yo.</title>
    <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/tags/wednesday/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Wednesday on Tryna Get Less Fat, Yo.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fat.cliff1976.net/tags/wednesday/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 05 27</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-05-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-05-27/</guid>
      <description>Another beautiful day.
I crossed onto one of the islands in Danube. Took another look at one of those sheltery things I&amp;rsquo;d seen there previously. Still creepy. The channels were peaceful. There was a weird Yoda/Nosferatu hybrid graffito thing.
Snaps:
Your browser does not support the HTML5 Video element.  Route:
Machine(s): none (street) Time: 1:30 Distance: 6.0 km Calories: 658 Calories from fat: 37% Average Heart Rate: 106 Maximum Heart Rate: 123 Fat Burn: 1:20 Fitness: 0:10 Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 05 20</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-05-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-05-20/</guid>
      <description>Sure don&amp;rsquo;t remember teleporting home from Neupfarrplatz! Maybe it has something do with the giant golden sperm attacking the city.
Snaps:
Route:
Machine(s): none (street) Time: 1:15 Distance: 5.56 km? Calories: 481 Calories from fat: 40% Average Heart Rate: 101 Maximum Heart Rate: 122 Fat Burn: 1:12 Fitness: 0:03 Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 05 13</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-05-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-05-13/</guid>
      <description>A pretty dreary morning (most of them have been lately after those glorious weeks in March and April). But walked along the Wöhrd and took the stairs right down the water line in a few places. It&amp;rsquo;s been somewhat rainy, but the river wasn&amp;rsquo;t running particularly high or fast. I got a special treat: watching a barge with a lift switch out a riverway sign.
Snaps:
Route:
Machine(s): none (street) Time: 1:05 Distance: 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 04 29</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-04-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-04-29/</guid>
      <description>A moderately rainy morning after several weeks of almost no rain. No inspiring photographs today; my walk was through neighborhoods and apartment complexes.
I did notice the Singh Indischer Markt seems to have been replaced with a Middle Eastern market of some kind.
And somehow I must have lost GPS connectivity along the way there towards the end, because I definitely did not sneak through anyone&amp;rsquo;s house. Promise.
Snaps:
Route:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 04 15</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-04-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-04-15/</guid>
      <description>Cool early morning.
No snaps this time &amp;ndash; nothing really spoke to me.
Route:
Machine(s): none (street) Time: 71 mins Distance: 5.69 km Calories: 548 Calories from fat: 37% Average Heart Rate: 108 Maximum Heart Rate: 132 Fat Burn: 64 mins Fitness: 7 min Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 04 08</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-04-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-04-08/</guid>
      <description>Another beautiful day.
Did a loop behind the Max-Straße McD&amp;rsquo;s up and down some steps for fun. It was not very fun.
Snaps:
Route:
It would appear that my app did not save my route. It was from our house through the southern end of the Altstadt with some loops in the western part, and back home via the south bank of the Danube.
Machine(s): none (street) Time: 81 mins Distance: 6.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 04 01</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-04-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-04-01/</guid>
      <description>Another beautiful day. Got started earlier than normal thanks to an 8:00 meeting. 2nd in a row. Work is a pain like that.
Remember: you can get gelbe Säcke at the HEM Tankstelle on Friedenstraße 24 hours a day!
Route:
Machine(s): none (street) Time: 47 mins Distance: 4.15 km Calories: 464 Calories from fat: 25% Average Heart Rate: 123 Maximum Heart Rate: 141 Fat Burn: 12 mins Fitness: 35 mins Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 03 25</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-03-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-03-25/</guid>
      <description>Another beautiful day. Went south up to the Alte Mälzerei, then west through Kumpfmühl and south back into the Alstadt via the Schloßpark.
Route:
Machine(s): none (street) Time: 1 hour 10 mins Distance: 5.18 km Calories: 637 Calories from fat: 34% Average Heart Rate: 111 Maximum Heart Rate: 135 Fat Burn: 65 mins Fitness: 5 mins Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 03 18</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-03-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-03-18/</guid>
      <description>Cloudy and foggy early morning weather made a rather unattractive city walk behind a residential complex somewhat spooky.
Route:
Machine(s): none (street) Time: 52 mins Distance: 4.67 km Calories: 475 Calories from fat: 31% Average Heart Rate: 117 Maximum Heart Rate: 130 Fat Burn: 32 mins Fitness: 20 mins Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 03 11</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-03-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-03-11/</guid>
      <description>First workout again after the big weekend activity with Democrats Abroad. Back on the horse.
Machine(s): elliptical Time: 41 minutes Distance: 4.3 km Calories: 375 Calories from fat: 28% Average Heart Rate: 117 Maximum Heart Rate: 129 Fat Burn: 21 minutes Fitness: 20 minutes Weight: not measured </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 03 04</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-03-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-03-04/</guid>
      <description>Machine(s): elliptical Time: 40 minutes Distance: 4.37 km Calories: 338 Calories from fat: 33% Average Heart Rate: 113 Maximum Heart Rate: 120 Fat Burn: 37 minutes Fitness: 3 minutes Weight: not measured </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 02 12</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-02-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-02-12/</guid>
      <description>Second weigh-in of the year. Gained a pound(ish). I think the increassed activity these past two weeks has made me hungrier, and I&amp;rsquo;m eating more. Guess that&amp;rsquo;s OK as long as it&amp;rsquo;s the low-cal stuff.
Machine(s): elliptical Settings: incline 6, resistance 1 (but that doesn&#39;t seem right; I thought it was incline 1, resistance 8) Time: 42 minutes Calories: 374 Calories from fat: 30% Average Heart Rate: 117 Maximum Heart Rate: 127 Fat Burn: 22 minutes Fitness: 20 minutes Weight: 114 kg </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 02 05</title>
      <link>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-02-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fat.cliff1976.net/posts/workouts/2020-02-05/</guid>
      <description>First weigh-in of the year. Surprisingly: I&amp;rsquo;m down about 9.5 kg from June 2019 and 8 kg from October 2019 at the doctor&amp;rsquo;s office. Either:
 one (or both?) of the scales are miscalibrated, or I have lost weight by going on vacation in December (???), or something evil is happening and I&amp;rsquo;m losing weight for bad reasons.  Machine(s): elliptical Settings: dunno Time: 42 minutes Calories: 399 Calories from fat: 26% Average Heart Rate: 120 Maximum Heart Rate: 131 Fat Burn: 9 minutes Fitness: 33 minutes Weight: 113.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
