<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Friday on Hello Friend NG</title>
    <link>http://fatcliff1976net.netlify.app/tags/friday/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Friday on Hello Friend NG</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://fatcliff1976net.netlify.app/tags/friday/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 06 05</title>
      <link>http://fatcliff1976net.netlify.app/posts/workouts/2020-06-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://fatcliff1976net.netlify.app/posts/workouts/2020-06-05/</guid>
      <description>It was another Kurzarbeit day. I had to skip my walks a couple days this week, so I stretched this out one longer on purpose. I made it up to the Fernsehturm in Ziegetsdorf, walked parallel to the A3 towards the Uniklinikum and back. It was threatening to rain most of the way with some nice patches of sun to break things up.
Snaps:
Route:
Machine(s): none (street) Time: 2:10 Distance: 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 04 17</title>
      <link>http://fatcliff1976net.netlify.app/posts/workouts/2020-04-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://fatcliff1976net.netlify.app/posts/workouts/2020-04-16/</guid>
      <description>Lots of pics and a longer route this time — thanks Kurzarbeit — to make up for yesterday&amp;rsquo;s slacking.
This was the first time I explored the Unterer Wöhrd &amp;ldquo;off-road.&amp;rdquo; Found some shelters near the Jugendherberge that looked a little spooky. I don&amp;rsquo;t know whether those are someone&amp;rsquo;s emergency shelter or just a relaxing hideaway.
Snaps:
Route:
Machine(s): none (street) Time: 91 mins Distance: 7.25 km Calories: 661 Calories from fat: 37% Average Heart Rate: 106 Maximum Heart Rate: 120 Fat Burn: 87 mins Fitness: 4 min Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 04 10</title>
      <link>http://fatcliff1976net.netlify.app/posts/workouts/2020-04-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://fatcliff1976net.netlify.app/posts/workouts/2020-04-10/</guid>
      <description>Another beautiful day. Good Friday, even.
Snaps:
Route:
Machine(s): none (street) Time: 71 mins Distance: 6.1 km Calories: 504 Calories from fat: 39% Average Heart Rate: 105 Maximum Heart Rate: 121 Fat Burn: 70 mins Fitness: 1 min Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 04 03</title>
      <link>http://fatcliff1976net.netlify.app/posts/workouts/2020-04-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://fatcliff1976net.netlify.app/posts/workouts/2020-04-03/</guid>
      <description>Another beautiful day. No 8:00 meeting this morning, thankyouverymuch.
The Westhafen was quite still. Erdbeer-Rhabarber Streuselküchle are back at the Beck.
Route:
Machine(s): none (street) Time: 66 mins Distance: 5.48 km Calories: 541 Calories from fat: 33% Average Heart Rate: 112 Maximum Heart Rate: 124 Fat Burn: 49 mins Fitness: 17 mins Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 03 27</title>
      <link>http://fatcliff1976net.netlify.app/posts/workouts/2020-03-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://fatcliff1976net.netlify.app/posts/workouts/2020-03-27/</guid>
      <description>Another beautiful day.
Some snaps: Route:
Machine(s): none (street) Time: 1 hour 16 mins Distance: 7.1 km Calories: 620 Calories from fat: 33% Average Heart Rate: 111 Maximum Heart Rate: 133 Fat Burn: 59 mins Fitness: 17 mins Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bad Abbach 2020 03 20</title>
      <link>http://fatcliff1976net.netlify.app/posts/walks/bad_abbach_2020-03-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://fatcliff1976net.netlify.app/posts/walks/bad_abbach_2020-03-20/</guid>
      <description>This was the last chance to leave town before the Ausgangsbeschränkung went into effect at midnight tonight, so we took it. We also saw
 where our pal gets all those beautiful mystical forest shots of his dogs, and some ancient Celtic mystery forest stuff [cue the spooky music], and the foundations of an old Roman bathhouse as the ruins from a Villa Rustica  Route:
Time: 121 mins Distance: 7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 03 20</title>
      <link>http://fatcliff1976net.netlify.app/posts/workouts/2020-03-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://fatcliff1976net.netlify.app/posts/workouts/2020-03-20/</guid>
      <description>Another beautiful day. Tried out Kumpfmühl for the first time; some nice neighborhoods there.
Route:
Machine(s): none (street) Time: 58 mins Distance: 5.05 km Calories: 576 Calories from fat: 29% Average Heart Rate: 116 Maximum Heart Rate: 132 Fat Burn: 28 mins Fitness: 36 mins Weight: not weighed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workout 2020 02 07</title>
      <link>http://fatcliff1976net.netlify.app/posts/workouts/2020-02-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://fatcliff1976net.netlify.app/posts/workouts/2020-02-07/</guid>
      <description>This one proved that I can be at the gym at 7:02, get a decent amount of time in on the machine of my choice (they were all empty), and still walk back home with time to change into work clothes for a bike ride into work by 9:00. Or close enough to it.
Machine(s): elliptical Settings: dunno Time: 42 minutes Calories: 408 Calories from fat: 29% Average Heart Rate: 121 Maximum Heart Rate: 133 Fat burn: 17 minutes Fitness: 25 minutes Weight: not measured </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
